Guide to the Solomon Feferman papers SC0907
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2018-045
  - Professional
    - Correspondence, Programs / Vienna 1993 Aug 22-23 / Buno 1993 Aug 23-27 [KGC 93] / Prague 1993 Aug 23-Sept 3 / Warsaw 1993 3-9 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Randll Holmes (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - KGS (K. Godel Society) Meetings/Invitations (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Douglas Brown (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Antonelli Recommendtions (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Boolos Conference-Notre Dame, 1998 Apr 16-18 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - 20th World Congress of Philosophy Boston, 1998 Aug 10-16 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - AMS/MAA/ASL Mtg. San Diego, 1996 Jan 1 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Cambridge Boolos Symposium ASL Meet Godel eds. Meet, 1997 Mar 21-25 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Uppersala Lecture, 1996 Aug 18-21 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Godel's Dialectica Interpretation and its two-way stretch [Lecture for KGC 93 Buno-Aug 93] / Hodel correspond, Kreisel corresponence, 1993 Aug (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - FAX Vieuna (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Maison Suger (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - CASBS/ Bellagio Forms, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Sabbagh (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Proof Theory Course Notes 293A, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Bibliograpgic and Copyright Data for "In the Light of Logic" / Editorial Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - OUP-Promotion Today (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Contact with Pabeishens (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - OUP Memo of Agreement Godel Works IV + V (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Kreisel's "unwinding" program + partial draft "apprenticeship of a logician" (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - My route to Arithematization (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - In the light of logic-original papers (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Part Four Proof Theoetical Tools: 11. What logic has to tell us about math proofs. 12. Three reviews in proof thery (Tarski, Shutte, Pranits) 13. What rests on what? The proof theory analysis of math. 14/ Godel's dialectica interp. And its two-way stretch (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Part Six: 18. Intensionality in Math 19. Between constructive and classical math (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - WKL Elimination Notes (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - WKL/WKL+ Dialectica (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Book / Wilfried Suggestions / Some relevant papers (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Book Ch IV-V (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Computation on ADTs Transparencies (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - 8th Gidel Lecture "Occupations and Preoccupations with Godel: his works and the work" ASL meet, Cambridge, MA + relevant papers, 1997 Mar 22 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Intuition vs Monsters transparences, notes, correspondence / world congress of philosophy, Boston, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - "Logic, Logics, and Logicians" / Boolos Symposium Notre Dame / Transparencies, 1998 Apr 15-18 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Roskilde Lecture Transparencies, 1997 Oct (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Logics for Termination Correctness of Functional Programs (I) Transparencies (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Logics for Termination Correctness of Functional Programs (II) Strength PRA Leeds, Proof Theory Transparencies, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Higher classes in Explicit Maths. Transparencies-Castiglioncello, 1998 Oct (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Applicative Theories and Various types-Transparencies Lecture ESSLI, 1997 Aug (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - NSF Grants (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Meetings (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence
    - Handwritten Letters (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Handwritten Letters II (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Generalizing K-local Functions (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Reps of Ordinals-other people (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Cates Theory Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Gen, Recu. Theory Unified Ind. Defense (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Grilliot Connectios between general of recur. Theory (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Gandy-Hyland / Kreisel Lecture (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - PG -Smith Prelim Committee Work-Reviews (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Cecursion in Finite Types Feferman, Warien, Schwichtenberg, Herrington, McQueen (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Visits (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence Feferman, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Handwritten Letters III (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Handwritten Letters IV, 1967-1968 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Current, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Meetings-Trips, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Mailings, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Mailing Lists (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Currnet / Refile, 1979-1982 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Very Current-Unsorted / Refile, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Ordinals / Proof Theory / Nice Talk (Correspondence) / Ordinals Talk, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Carol Rovane / Patrick Suppes, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Beeson / Cover Kreisel to Beeson (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Extended Model Theory + Etc (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - ID- Project Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Self-Ref Curry Paper / Fitch / Bouidw (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Fitch (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Original Type-Free I (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Cornell Letter, 1990 Oct 25 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - A.Church Letter "Turning in the land of O(z)" (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Refile (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - ASL-Meeting Stanford / Logic-C.S-Linguistics / Paris Meet / Chicago, 1985 Jul / 1986 Mar 22 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Talcott / Combrase Seminar Party (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Category Theory (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - G.K.-Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - G.K Correspondence, etc, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - GK Letters, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - G.K Correspondence, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - GK, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - GK, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Letters (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - C. 15 Business Misc, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - 0, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - 0, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - 0, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - 0, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Unlabeled, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Sieg / Buchholy / Pohlens (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Nehes-Motolashu-Mukkas (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Barwise (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Sets and Classes with rely-membership / Category Theory (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - To Kreisel (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Jenoslow-Larson (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Salbagh Letters, en / Frevich group (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Kreisel / GK / Correspond, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - 0, 1980-1984 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Reprints
    - Feferman Ph.D Dissertation UCD 1957 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Fund. Math: The first order properties of poducts of algebraic systems w/Vaught (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Proof Theory Article for SEP (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - JSL: Transtfinite Recursive Progressions of Aximatic Theories Avigad, Jeremy (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Abs Unsolved Probs Proof Sheets (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Weyl Vindicated: Das Kontinuem 70 Years Later (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Predicative Provability in Set Theory, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Persistent and Invariant Forums… w/Kreisel, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Autonomous Transfinite progressions and…, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Comp Math: Persistent and Invariant Forumlas for Outer Extensions, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - JSL: Systems of Predicative Analysis, II, Representations of Orrdinals, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Act, Cong. Int. Math.: Ordinals and Functional in Proof Theory, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Hereditarily Replete Functionals Over the Ordinals, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Formal Theories for Transfinite Iterations of Gen. IDS, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Ordinals Associated with theories for one ID, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Applictions of Many-sorted Interpolation Theorems, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Predicatively Reducible Systems of Set Theory, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Some Formal theories for the unlimited theory of structures and categories, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Two notes on abstract model theory U, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Fund. Math: Two notes on abstract model theory II, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Indductive Schemata and Recursively Continuous Functionals, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Impredicitivity of the Existence of the largest divisible subgroup…, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Comparison of some type-free Semantic and Math Theories (draft), 1976 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Categorical Foundations and Foundation of Category Theory, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Handbook of Math Logic: Theories of Finite Type Related to M. Practice, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Generating Schemes for partial recursively continuous functionals, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Comp Math: Recursion in Total Functionals of Finite Type, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Essays on Math Phil. Logic: Generalizing Set-Theoretical Model Theory, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - The logic of mathematical discovery vs the logical structual of math, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - What does logic have to tell us about math proofs?, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Proof Theory Schutte, Review, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Godel's incompleteness Theoreums and the reflection closure of theories, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Constructive Theories of Functions and Classes, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Monotone Inductive Defintions, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - The logic of mathematical discovery vs the logical structual of math, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Iterated Inductive Fixed-Point Theories: Application to Hancook's Conjecture, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Inductively Presented Systems and the Formation of Metamathematics, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Philos. Natur. Kurt Godel: Conviction and Caution, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - JSL, Toward Useful Type-Free Theories, I, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Persp. In Math: Foundational Ways, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Between Constructive and Classical Math, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - J. Of Phil. Logic: Intensionality in Math, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Syntese: Working Foundations, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Infinity in Math: Is Cantor Neccesary?, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Weyl Dindicated: "Fas Kontinuum" 70 Years Later, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - JSL: Hilbert's Program Relativized: Proof-theoretical and…, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Turning in the land of O(z), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Remarks for the "Trends in Logic" Panel Discussion, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Finitary inductively presented logics, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Infinity in Mathematics: Is Cantor Necessary?, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Polymorphoc Typed Lambda-Calculi in a Type-Free Ax. Framework, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - JSL: Reflecting on Incompleteness, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Logics for termination and corectness of functional programs, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Logics for termination and corectness of functional programs, II. Logics and Strength PRA, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Turning's "Oracle", 1992 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - What rests on what?, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Jean Van Heijenoort, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - A new approach to abstract data types, I Informal development, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - A new approach to abstract data types, II: Computation on ADTs as Ordinary Computation, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Why a little bit goes a long way: Logical Foundations…, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Logics for termination and correctness of functional programs, II. Logics of strength PRA, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Working Foundations-91, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Systems of EM with non-construction u-operator. Part 1, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Julia Bowman Robinson 1919-1985, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Definedness, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - APLA: Systems of Explicit Mathematics with non-constructive u-operator Part II, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - LMCS Tarski's Influence on Computer Science, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - In The Enc Of Phil. Supplement: Proof Theory, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - APAL: Computations on Abstract Data Types extensional approach, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - 7th SLS: Three Conceptual Problems That Bug Me, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Godel's Program for new axioms: Why, where, how, and what?, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Kreisel's "Unwinding" Program, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Challenges to Predicative Foundations of Arithmetic w/Hellman, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Proof Theory Since 1960, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - 8th Godel Lecture: Occupations and Preoccuptions with Godel: His Works and the work, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Theoria: My Route To Arithimetization, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Handbook of Proof Theory: "Dialectica" w/Avigad, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Kurt Schutte's Way, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - NDJFL: Logic, Logics, and Logicism, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - BSL: In Memoriam: Kenneth Jon Barwise: 1942-2000 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Highlights in Proof Theory, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Does Reductive Proof Theory have a viable rationale?, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Synthese: Mathematical Intution vs Mathematical Monsters, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Proof Theory: Relationships between Constructive Predicative and Classical Systems of Analsysi, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Proof Theory: The Significance of Weyl's "Das Kontiuum", 2000 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - APAL: The Unfolding of Non-finitist Arithmetic W/Strahm, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Rolf Schock Symp: Are there absolutely unsolable problems?, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Alfred Tarski and a Watershed Meeting in Logic: Cornell, 1957, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Comments on "Predicativity as a Phil. Position"" by G. Hellman, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - APAL: Tarski's Conception of Logic, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - In: 100 Years Of Russell's Paradox: Typical Amgiguity: Trying To Have Your Cake and Eat it Too, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Storia Della Scienza: The development of programs…, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Goldstein: Incompleteness: The Proof and Paradox of Kurt Godel Review, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - BSL: The Godel Editorial Project: A Synposis, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Notices of the AMS: The impact of the incompleteness Theorems on Mathematics, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - What kind of logic is "Independence Friendly" logic?, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Phil. Math: Are There Absolutely Unsolvable Problems? Godel's Dichotomy, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Harmonious logic: Craig's interpolation theorem and its descendants, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Dialectica: Lieber Herr Bernays!, Lieber Herr Godel!, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - J of Phil: Godel, Nagel, Minds and Machines, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - On the strength of semi-constructive theories, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Ways of Proof Theory: The Proof Theory of Class and Constructive Inductive Defintions, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - FHCT'II: Two PhD Students for the Price of One, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Enriched Stratified Systems for the Found of Category Theory, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - On Rereading Van Heijenoort's Selected Essays, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Alan Turing: His Worked Impact: SF Returns to Turing's Thesis: Ordinal Logics, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Reprints (Box 18)
  - Math Department
    - Kreisel-C.V-Bibliography (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Kreisel-Zll Reviews (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Kreisel (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Kreisel Annotated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Feferman (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Chapter 2 (Part 1, 3, 4, 5) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Chapter 3-5 parts (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Fef-Mont. Notes (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - What does logic have to tell us about math proofs? (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Feferman (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Model Theroetic Logics-Final (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Logic and Foundations Looping Back and Looping Forward (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Feferman (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Kreisel (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Kresiel-Predicatiuity (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 75-Clermount-FD SIECIL / London, Ontario ICCMPS (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Jersulaem, 1975 Dec (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - A Language and Axioms for Explicit Mathematics, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Orleans Meetings, 1972 Sep (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Meetings Visists Fineland/Europe (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Reno-ASL Meetings (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Proof Theory / Friedman (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Kreisel Letters, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Kreisel Letters, 1961-1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Pletek III (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Platek Thesis (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - NSF Renewal (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - NSF Orogress Report, 1982 Oct (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - NSF Proposal "Unfolding Schematic Formal Systems", 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Feferman Minutes Grants Proposal NSF, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - NSF Proposal Systems of Variable Type (With Maron and Talcott), 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - NSF-Final Report, 1998 Nov (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - NSF-Joint with Talcott/Mason Prject Proposal, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - NSF-CCR93293 Progress Reports (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - NSF Proposal Supplements Applications of Dialectics Interpretation (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Minutes/Feferman Proposal, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Mints NSF Proposal, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - SF NSF Proposals 1991, 1986-1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - NSF Gaul, 1987-1989 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - ARO (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - ARO to 1967 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Group Meet File + Talks (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Kleene Neets AOA Meet (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Mailing Lists Logic People (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Fellowship Business (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Fellowship Applications (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Venter, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Goodman (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Bishop-Harrison etc. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Ch IV-W81 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Ch V-W81 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Jeroslow, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Larson (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Book / I, II, (Part) III-V (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Maths as objective subjectivity (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Ch I-W81 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Ch II-W81 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Ch III-Write 81 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Math Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Engebnisse Editorial Sprine, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Engebnisse Editorial Work / Correspondences, 1981-1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Crackpots Others (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence 1989 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - MSRI-Logic Year, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Humanities Center Application (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Publications: Reprinted "in math" Philosophical Topics (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Feferman-Billet Status (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - S.F Math-Philosophy Split of Position (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Faculty Annuel Report, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Annual Faculty Report, 1986-1991 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - C.V. / Bibliography (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Me-Stanford (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Fellowship Info (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Weyhrauch-Thesis (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Bernays Abhandlungen, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Skolem, 1922 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Skolem, 1928 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Skolem, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Skolem, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Skolem, 1938 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Skolem, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Work on intuition VI Drafts (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Work on Intuition VI Hibbert (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Work on intuition IV Text (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Work on intution I (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Monk Appointment, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Logic Position (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Grisha Mints / 3rd CSLI Workshop on Logic, Rationality Intelligent Interaction, 2014 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Current Winter, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Suppes, Pat Interview, 1995 Apr 12 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Phil dept Logic Search, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Palmy Days For Logic at Stanford (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Logic Curriculum-Philosophy and Math (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Logic Memo, 1993 Mar (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Finn Case-Deposition, 1991 Jul 26 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - History of Logic Positions at Stanford (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - History of Logic Positions at Stanford (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Logic Curriculum-Philosophy Dept, 2000-201 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Philosophy Dept Needs Assessments Logical Program, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Phil 168/268 Theories of Truth Winter, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Phil 168/268 Handouts (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Phil 168/268 Theories of Truth Spring, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Phil 290.5 Theories of Truth Seminar U.C. Berkeley Spring, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Phil 12: Godel's Theorem, Minds and Machine, Autumn, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Phil 12: Godel's Theorem, Minds and Machine, Autumn Notes and Materials, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Godel's Theorem Minds and Machine U.C Berkeley Spring Semester Lecture Notes taken by Chris Wilson, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Phil 12: Godel's Theorem, Minds and Machine, Misc (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - MIT, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Logic Seminar W15-Phil 391-9 / w15 Math 391-1 Formal Semantics, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Logic Seminar Aut, 214-215 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Logic Seminar Fall, 2015 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - E.W Beth Lectures Mar, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - F. Fest, 1998 Dec 11-13 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Reflections (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Logic Program (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Phil 168/268 Theories of Trut (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Audiovisual Material
    - Tarski 2006 Lecture 2 / Solomon Fefferman "The 'Logic' Question", 13_01; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 13)
    - Tarski 2006 Lecture 1 / Solomon Feferman "Truth Unbound", 13_02; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 13)
    - Personal - Family, garden, Recipes, taxes, dreams…, 1990 July 3; 13_03; 1 Micro floppydisk (Box 13)
    - Tarski 2006 Lecture 3 / Solomon Feferman "Real Computation", 13_04; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 13)
    - Schock Photos, 13_05; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 13)
    - Feferman Disk / #3, 13_06; 2 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 13)
    - Sol's Disks / HP DeskJet 970C Series, 2002 Nov 23; 13_07; 2 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 13)
    - Copy of Anita's "New World" All Tarski Stuff / All personal stuff, 1998 July 6 / Jan 4; 13_08; 1 zip disk(s) (Box 13)
    - Files from Eudera (1) DSS Personal Information, 13_09; 1 floppy disk(s) (3.5 inch) (Box 13)
    - Copied Folders on / Papers / Recommendations / Tarski files / Godel and Tarski, 2003 Jan 4; 13_10; 1 zip disk(s) (Box 13)
    - Folders: Papers, Reccommendations, Tarski Files…, 2001 March 1; 13_11; 1 zip disk(s) (Box 13)
    - Feferfest - Sol's 70th Birthday, 1998 Dec; 19_01; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 19)
    - Feferman (3) Reflections, 19_02; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 19)
    - Feferman (II) Reflections on Relationship between Constructive predicative and classical analysis, 1997 Nov 1; 19_03; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 19)
    - Feferman II The Significance of Herman Weyl's Das Konfinunums, 1997 Oct 31; 19_04; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 19)
    - A. Barwise etal on CSLI - Polya Hall, 1983 Sep 1; 19_05; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 19)
    - Feferman Lecture 1: Highlights in Proof Theory Hilbert's First Formation, 1997 Oct 31; 19_06; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 19)
    - ASL Symp. On Phils. Signal of Godel's Inc. Theorems: Tape I, 1965 April 29-30; 19_07; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 19)
    - Sol on Do We Need New Axioms, 19_08; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 19)